Guide to the Vassar College Subject Files, 1864–2023
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- V. C. Lukens Memorial Scholarship (Folder 19.25)
- V. C. Madrigal Group/Madrigal Singers (Folder 19.26)
- V. C. Magazine Subscription Bureau (Folder 19.27)
- V. C. Magoon, Rev. Dr., Art Collection (Folder 19.28)
- V. C. Marking System (Folder 19.29)
- V. C. Martial Arts Club (Folder 19.30)
- V. C. Mary Conover Mellon Foundation. American College Women, Miscellaneous Material (Folder 19.31)
- V. C. Mary Conover Mellon Foundation. Conference on the American College (Folder 19.32-19.33)
- V. C. Mary Conover Mellon Foundation. Measurement and Evaluation of Change in College Women (Folder 19.34)
- V. C. Mary Conover Mellon Foundation. Perry Lectures (Folder 19.35)
- V. C. Mary Conover Mellon Foundation. Publications on releases on Mellon Studies (Folder 19.36)
- V. C. Mary Conover Mellon Foundation. Student Mellon Committee (Folder 19.37)
- V. C. Mary Conover Mellon Foundation. Values and Mores of Students (Folder 19.38)
- V. C. Mary Conover Mellon Foundation. V. C. Attitude Inventory and Figure Preference (Folder 19.39)
- V. C. Mary Conover Mellon Fund for Music Literature (Folder 19.40)
- V. C. Masters Degrees, see also: V. C. Degrees (Folder 19.41)
- V. C. Masters Theses (Folder 19.42)
- V. C. Mastodon (Folder 19.43)
- V. C. Matthew Club Reading Group (Folder 20.1)
- V. C. Matthew Vassar Lectures (Folder 20.2)
- V. C. Matthew Vassar Scholars (Folder 20.3)
- V. C. Medals (Folder 20.4)
- V. C. Mellon Grants (Andrew W. Mellon Foundation) (Folder 20.5)
- V. C. Mental Hygiene (Folder 20.6)
- V. C. Message Center (Folder 20.7)
- V. C. Microcomputers, see also: V. C. Computers (Folder 20.8)
- V. C. Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools. Evaluations (self-Study) (Folder 20.9)
- V. C. Mid-winter Holiday (Folder 20.10)
- V. C. Mill Cove Lake, see: V. C. Lakes
- V. C. Millay Society (Folder 20.11)
- V. C. Millstone (Folder 20.12)
- V. C. Million Dollar Development Program, see: V. C. Development Group
- V. C. Million Dollar Endowment Fund, 1916? (Folder 20.13)
- V. C. Mills Gate (Folder 20.14)
- V. C. Mini-courses (non-credit), undated, 1976-1984 (Folder 20.15)
- V. C. Mini-courses (non-credit), 1985- (Folder 20.16)
- V. C. Minor Mention, undated-1935 (Folder 20.17)
- V. C. Minor Mention, 1936-1959 (Folder 20.18)
- V. C. Minor Mention, 1960-1962 (Folder 20.19)
- V. C. Minor Mention, 1963-1967 (Folder 20.20)
- V. C. Minor Mention, 1968-1971 (Folder 20.21)
- V. C. Minor Mention, 1972- (Folder 20.22)
- V. C. Moderate, Independent and Conservative Alliance (MICA) (Folder 20.23)
- V. C. Mohonk Trip (Folder 20.24)
- V. C. Moore, J. Leverett, Fund for Research in Classics (Folder 20.25)
- V. C. Mottoes (Folder 20.26)
- V. C. Movies and Moving Picture Equipment (Folder 20.27)
- V. C. Multidisciplinary Program, see also: V. C. Interdepartmental courses (Folder 20.28)
- V. C. Murphy Farmhouse Arts and Crafts Center, see also: V. C. Food Co-operatives (Folder 20.29)
- V. C. Museums. (General) (Folder 20.30)
- V. C. Museums. Anthropology (Folder 20.31)
- V. C. Museums. Classics (Folder 20.32)
- V. C. Museums. Geology (Folder 20.33)
- V. C. Museums. Geology and Mineralogy, Cabinet of (Folder 20.34)
- V. C. Museums. Music (Folder 20.35)
- V. C. Museums. Natural History (Folder 20.36)
- V. C. Museums. Plant Science (Folder 20.37)
- V. C. Museums. Social (Folder 20.38)
- V. C. Music, School of, see also: V. C. Departments. Music (Folder 20.39)
- V. C. Music and Records (Folder 20.40)
- V. C. Music Library see: V. C. Library - Music Library
- V. C. New Dimensions, Committee on, see also: Yale-Vassar Study (Folder 21.1)
- V. C. News Office, see also: V. C. Communications, Dept of, V. C. Publications, Bureau of, V. C. Public Relations, Office of; V. C. Press and Information Office; V. C. College Relations Office of (Folder 21.2)
- V. C. Night Owls (Folder 21.3)
- V. C. Norrie, Margaret Lewis - Scholarship (Folder 21.4-21.5)
- V. C. North Gate (Folder 21.6)
- V. C. Nourse, Mary Pemberton Fund (Folder 21.7)
- V. C. Noyes Memorial Fund (Folder 21.8)
- V. C. Nursery School (Folder 21.9)
- V. C. Occupation Bureau, see: V. C. Career Planning and Placement Office of, V. C. Vocational Bureau
- V. C. Off-campus Studies (formerly Field Work Office) (Folder 21.10)
- V. C. Office of Religious Activities and Chaplaincy Services (Folder 21.11)
- V. C. Official Publications (Folder 21.12)
- V. C. Ohemaa (anthropology organization) (Folder 21.13)
- V. C. Omgim Club (Oh my God, it's Monday) (Folder 21.14)
- V. C. Orchestra (Folder 21.15)
- V. C. Organ (Folder 21.16)
- V. C. Organization of Untenured Teachers (O.U.T.) (Folder 21.17)
- V. C. Outdoor Classroom (Folder 21.18)
- V. C. Outdoor Plays (Folder 21.19)
- V. C. Outdoor Theatre (Folder 21.20)
- V. C. Outing Club (Folder 21.21)
- V. C. Owl and Torch (Campus Guides) (Folder 21.22)
- V. C. Parents Weekend, see: V. C. Sophomore Fathers...
- V. C. Parietals (Folder 21.23)
- V. C. Parking (Folder 21.24)
- V. C. Pass Credit or Pass Fail Courses, see: V. C. Independent Programs
- V. C. Pay Day (Folder 21.25)
- V. C. Peace (Course on) (Folder 21.26)
- V. C. Peace Council (Folder 21.27)
- V. C. Peace Reading List (Folder 21.28)
- V. C. Periodicals (Folder 21.29)
- V. C. Persian Gulf War (Folder 21.30)
- V. C. Personnel Office (Folder 21.31)
- V. C. Personnel Research Bureau (Folder 21.32)
- V. C. Peter Cottontails (story telling group) (Folder 21.33)
- V. C. Phi Beta Kappa (Folder 21.34)
- V. C. Phi Beta Kappa Lectures (Folder 21.35)
- V. C. Philalethean Society (Folder 21.36-21.37)
- V. C. Philalethean Society Programs (Folder 21.38)
- V. C. Philaletheis. Chapter Alpha (Folder 21.39)
- V. C. Physicians (Folder 21.40)
- V. C. Picture Bureau (Folder 21.41)
- V. C. Pictures (Folder 21.42)
- V. C. Plaintiff (Folder 21.43)
- V. C. Plant Operations, see also: V. C. Facilities Operations (Folder 21.44)
- V. C. Plaster Casts (Folder 21.45)
- V. C. Plates, see: V. C. China and Silver
- V. C. Playing Cards (Folder 21.46)
- V. C. Poder Latino (Folder 21.47)
- V. C. Poetry Club (Folder 21.48)
- V. C. Poetry Contest (Folder 21.49)
- V. C. Political Association, see also: V. C. Consumers League (Folder 21.50)
- V. C. Political Inquiry Club (Folder 21.51)
- V. C. Postcards, see: V. C. Library Postcards
- V. C. Post Office (Folder 21.52)
- V. C. Poughkeepsie Relations with, see also: Arlington (Folder 21.53-21.55)
- V. C. Power Plant (Folder 21.56)
- V. C. Powerhouse Theatre (Folder 21.57)
- V. C. Poynter Fund, see also: V. C. Journalism Forum (Folder 21.58)
- V. C. Pratt Foundation (Folder 21.59)
- V. C. Prentiss Field, 1974- (Folder 21.60)
- V. C. Preparatory Department (Folder 21.61)
- V. C. President (Folder 21.62-21.63)
- V. C. President. Holiday Cards (Folder 21.64)
- V. C. President. Inaugural Speeches (Folder 21.65)
- V. C. President. (Raymond) Index to Vassar College; its Foundations, Aims... (Folder 21.66)
- V. C. Presidential Search Committees (Folder 21.67)
- V. C. President's Administrative Forum (Folder 21.68)
- V. C. President's Community Breakfast (Folder 21.69)
- V. C. President's Distinguished Visitor Program, 1981- (Folder 21.70)
- V. C. President's Task Force on Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Concerns (Folder 21.71)
- V. C. Press and Information Office, see also: V. C. Publication Bureau of; V. C. Public Relations, Office of; V. C. News Office; V. C. College Relations, Office of. (Folder 21.72)
- V. C. Press and Information On VC Campus (Folder 22.1)
- V. C. Press Releases--News From Vassar (current year by month) (Folder 22.2-22.13)
- V. C. Prints (Folder 22.14)
- V. C. Prizes, see also: by name of prize (Folder 22.15)
- [EMPTY] (Folder 22.16)
- V. C. Progressive Citizens of America (Folder 22.17)
- V. C. Prohibition Reading Room (Folder 22.18)
- V. C. Project, 1984 (Folder 22.19)
- V. C. Proms, see: V. C. Students. Proms
- V. C. Property (Folder 22.20)
- V. C. Prospectus (Folder 22.21)
- V. C. Prospectus Index (Folder 22.22)
- V. C. Proxy Review Committee (Folder 22.23)
- V. C. Public Relations Office, see also: V. C. Publication, Bureau of; V. C. News Office; V. C. Press and Information Office; V. C. College Relations, Office of (Folder 22.24)
- V. C. Public Safety, Dept of (Folder 22.25)
- V. C. Publication, Bureau of, see also: V. C. College Relations, Office of; V. C. Press and Information Office; V. C. News Office; V. C. Public Relations, Office of (Folder 22.26)
- V. C. Publications (Folder 22.27)
- V. C. Publications. 50th Anniversary (Folder 22.28)
- V. C. Publications. Reports of Officers (Folder 22.29)
- V. C. Publications. Semi-centennial Series (Folder 22.30)
- V. C. Publicity (Folder 22.31)
- V. C. Qui Vive (Folder 22.32)
- V. C. Race Relations Committee/Task Force (Folder 22.33)
- V. C. Radio Station (WVKR) (Folder 22.34)
- V. C. Raymond Avenue Ramblers (musical group) (Folder 22.35)
- V. C. Raymond Room (or Raymond Reading Room) (Folder 22.36)
- V. C. Reading and Pass Credit Courses, see: V. C. Independent Programs
- V. C. Reading Program for Incoming Freshmen, see: V. C. Freshman Orientation
- V. C. Recorder, see also: V. C. Registrar (Folder 22.37)
- V. C. Recycling (Folder 22.38)
- V. C. Refugees, see also: V. C. Faculty. Committees. Displaced Scholars (Folder 22.39)
- V. C. Registrar see also: V. C. Recorder (Folder 22.40)
- V. C. Regulations, see: V. C. College Regulations, V. C. Social Regulations
- V. C. Relief (Folder 22.41)
- V. C. Religious Life (Folder 22.42)
- V. C. Religious Life - Religious Weekends (Folder 22.43)
- V. C. Renaissance Colloquium, March 2-4, 1956 (Folder 22.44)
- V. C. Renaissance Seminar (in Italy), March 15-31, 1963 (Folder 22.45)
- V. C. Repertory Dance Theatre (Folder 22.46)
- V. C. Reports of Officers (Folder 22.47)
- V. C. Research (Folder 22.48)
- V. C. Residence, Director of (Folder 22.49)
- V. C. Residents, Board of (Folder 22.50)
- V. C. Rhodes Scholars (Folder 22.51)
- V. C. Richards, Ellen H. - Memorial Fund (Folder 22.52)
- V. C. Riding School (Folder 22.53)
- V. C. Russian Club (Folder 22.54)
- V. C. Russian Evening Program, see: V. C. Evening Russian Program
- V. C. Ruth Cutler Memorial Fund, see: V. C. Good Fellowship Club
- V. C. Salary Endowment Fund (Folder 22.55-22.59)
- V. C. Salmon Fund for Research. Lucy Maynard (General) (Folder 22.60)
- V. C. Salmon Fund for Research. Lucy Maynard. Grants (Folder 22.61)
- V. C. Salmon Fund for Research. Lucy Maynard. Publications (Folder 22.62)
- V. C. Sampler (Folder 22.63)
- V. C. Samuel Lemberg Foundation Lectures (Folder 22.64)
- V. C. Sawyer, Harriet - Fund (Folder 22.65)
- V. C. Schedule of Classes (general information) (Folder 22.66)
- V. C. Schedule of Exams (general) (Folder 22.67)
- V. C. Schedule of Exams, 1954/1955-1968/1969 (Folder 22.68)
- V. C. Schedule of Exams, 1969/1970- (Folder 22.69)
- V. C. Schedules (Folder 22.70)
- V. C. Scholarships, see also: V. C. Rhodes Scholars (Folder 22.71-22.73)
- V. C. Science courses (Folder 22.74)
- V. C. Science, Technology and Society Program (Folder 22.75)
- V. C. Science, Technology and Society Program. Lectures, Programs, etc. (Folder 22.76)
- V. C. Scrapbooks (Folder 22.77)
- V. C. Seal (Folder 23.1)
- V. C. Secretary (Folder 23.2)
- V. C. Security (Folder 23.3)
- V. C. Security. Campus Patrol (Folder 23.4)
- V. C. Self-evaluation Studies (Folder 23.5)
- V. C. Self-help Bureau, see: V. C. Students. Self-help
- V. C. Self-help Committee, see: V. C. Students. Self-help
- V. C. Senior Auction (Folder 23.6)
- V. C. Senior Class (Folder 23.7)
- V. C. Senior Convocation (Spring) (Folder 23.8)
- V. C. Senior Parlor (Folder 23.9)
- V. C. Senior Prom, see: V. C. Students. Prom
- V. C. Senior Sermons, see: V. C. Chapel Services, V. C. Baccalaureate Sermons
- V. C. Sexual Exploitation, Harassment (contains information re: CARES, Stop Rape Now Committee) (Folder 23.10)
- V. C. Sewage Disposal (Folder 23.11)
- V. C. Shakespeare Garden, see: V. C. Campus...
- V. C. Sharpe Memorial Lectures (Folder 23.12)
- V. C. Shop Club (Folder 23.13)
- V. C. Sigma Xi (Folder 23.14)
- V. C. Silver see: V. C. China and Silver
- V. C. Sitomer (Maurice) Lecture (Folder 23.15)
- V. C. Sloan Advisory Group (Folder 23.16)
- V. C. Sloan Grants (Folder 23.17)
- V. C. Smoking (Folder 23.18)
- V. C. Soccer Team (Folder 23.19)
- V. C. Social Events Board (Folder 23.20)
- V. C. Social Museum, see: V. C. Museum. Social
- V. C. Social Problems Club (Folder 23.21)
- V. C. Social Regulations (Folder 23.22)
- V. C. Societies, see: V. C. Clubs
- V. C. Society of Religious Inquiry (Folder 23.23)
- V. C. Solomon Amendment Rally Committee (Folder 23.24)
- V. C. Songs, 1865-1889 (Folder 23.25)
- V. C. Songs, 1890-1899 (Folder 23.26)
- V. C. Songs, 1900-1909 (Folder 23.27)
- V. C. Songs, 1910-1919 (Folder 23.28)
- V. C. Songs, 1920s (Folder 23.29)
- V. C. Songs, 1930s (Folder 23.30)
- V. C. Songs, 1940s (Folder 23.31)
- V. C. Songs, 1950s (Folder 23.32)
- V. C. Songs, 1960s (Folder 23.33)
- V. C. Songs. Alma Mater (by Amy Wentworth), 1898 (Folder 23.34)
- V. C. Songs. Alma Mater. History of (Folder 23.35)
- V. C. Songs. Alma Mater. Publication of, 1956 (Folder 23.36)
- V. C. Songs. Alma Mater. Various Renditions (Folder 23.37)
- V. C. Songs. Alma Mater. Words and Music (Folder 23.38)
- V. C. Songs. Baccalaureate Hymns, 1890s (Folder 23.39)
- V. C. Songs. Baccalaureate Hymns, 1900-1910 (Folder 23.40)
- V. C. Songs. Baccalaureate Hymns, 1911-1919 (Folder 23.41)
- V. C. Songs. Baccalaureate Hymns, 1920-1929 (Folder 23.42)
- V. C. Songs. Baccalaureate Hymns, 1930-1939 (Folder 23.43)
- V. C. Songs. Baccalaureate Hymns, 1940-1949 (Folder 23.44)
- V. C. Songs. Baccalaureate Hymns and Gaudeamus (Folder 23.45)
- V. C. Songs. Collections (Folder 23.46)
- V. C. Songs. Library Locations (call numbers, etc.) (Folder 23.47)
- V. C. Songs. Undated Manuscripts (Folder 23.48)
- V. C. Songs. Undated Miscellaneous (Folder 23.49)
- V. C. Sophomore Fathers'/Parents Weekend (Folder 23.50)
- V. C. Sophomore Joke Books, see also: V. C. Humor, Caricatures (Folder 23.51)
- V. C. South Africa Study Group (Folder 23.52)
- V. C. Souvenirs, see also: V. C. China and Silver (Folder 23.53)
- V. C. Spade (Folder 23.54)
- V. C. Special Projects, Office of (Folder 23.55)
- V. C. Special Services Program (Folder 23.56)
- V. C. Special Students, see: V. C. Students, Special
- V. C. Special Studies Courses, see: V. C. Interdepartmental Courses, V. C. Multidisciplinary Program
- V. C. Spoon, see: V. C. China and Silver
- V. C. Sporting the Oak (Folder 23.57)
- V. C. Staff Association, see also: V. C. Employees' Union, May 1973-March 1983 (Folder 23.58)
- V. C. Staff Association, April 1983- (Folder 23.59)
- V. C. Stationery (Folder 23.60)
- V. C. Stationery Store (Folder 23.61)
- V. C. Statistics, see also: V. C. Charts (Folder 23.62)
- V. C. Staton Scholarship Bequest (Folder 23.63)
- V. C. Statute of Instruction, see: V. C. Governance of Vassar College
- V. C. Stenographic Bureau (Folder 23.64)
- V. C. Step Beyond (Folder 23.65)
- V. C. Storer Fund (Folder 23.66)
- V. C. Student Activist Union (Folder 23.67)
- V. C. Student Activities Committee, see also: V. C. Student Entertainment Committee (Folder 23.68)
- V. C. Student Advisers (Folder 23.69)
- V. C. Student-Alumnae/i Relations (Folder 23.70)
- V. C. Student Conservative Association (Folder 23.71)
- V. C. Student Curriculum Committee (Folder 23.72)
- V. C. Student Entertainment Committee (VICE), see also: V. C. Student Activities Committee (Folder 23.73)
- V. C. Student Entertainment Committee The Vassar Collage (Folder 23.74)
- V. C. Student Exchange (Folder 23.75)
- V. C. Student - Faculty Council (Folder 23.76)
- V. C. Student, Faculty Parent Conference (Folder 23.77)
- V. C. Student Federalists (Folder 23.78)
- V. C. Student Furniture Exchange, see: V. C. Furniture Exchange
- V. C. Student Government Association, see also: V. C. Vassar Student Association (1979 - ), 1969 - 1979 (Folder 23.79)
- V. C. Student Handbook (Folder 23.80)
- V. C. Student Lecture Series (Folder 23.81)
- V. C. Student Liberal Association (Folder 23.82)
- V. C. Student Opera Workshop (Folder 23.83)
- V. C. Student Papers (Folder 23.84)
- V. C. Student Publications, see also: issues of student publications in the Vassariana publications collection (Folder 23.85)
- V. C. Student Relief (Folder 23.86)
- V. C. Student Rooms, see also: V. C. Students Housing (Folder 23.87)
- V. C. Student Scientific Conference, New York State (Folder 23.88)
- V. C. Student Task Force Against Racism, see: V. C. Race Relations
- V. C. Student Union (Folder 23.89)
- V. C. Student Withdrawals (Folder 23.90)
- V. C. Students (General) (Folder 23.91)
- V. C. Students. Athletics (Folder 23.92-23.93B)
- V. C. Students. Calendars, 1986 (Folder 23.94)
- V. C. Students. Computers (Folder 23.95)
- V. C. Students. Contest (Folder 23.96)
- V. C. Students. Costume (Folder 24.1)
- V. C. Students. Dances see: V. C. Students. Proms
- V. C. Students. Deaths (Folder 24.2)
- V. C. Students. Diet (Folder 24.3)
- V. C. Students. Drama. Antigone (Folder 24.4)
- V. C. Students. Drama. Antigone (Folder 24.5-24.6)
- V. C. Students. Earnings (Folder 24.7)
- V. C. Students. Exchange, see: V. C. Students, Exchange and Transfer
- V. C. Students. Expenses (Folder 24.8)
- V. C. Students. Extra-curricular Activities (Folder 24.9)
- V. C. Students. Fellowships/Grants (Folder 24.10)
- V. C. Students. Foreign Scholarship Drive Committee (Folder 24.11)
- V. C. Students. Health (Folder 24.12)
- V. C. Students. Honors and Prizes (Folder 24.13)
- V. C. Students. Housing (Folder 24.14)
- V. C. Students. Independent Study, see also: V. C. Independent Program (Folder 24.15)
- V. C. Students. Insurance (Folder 24.16)
- V. C. Students. Leaves (Folder 24.17)
- V. C. Students. Marriages, see also: V. C. Alumnae. Statistics, Vital (Folder 24.18)
- V. C. Students. Model League (Folder 24.19)
- V. C. Students. Morals (Folder 24.20)
- V. C. Students. Organization (Folder 24.21)
- V. C. Students. Pets (Folder 24.22)
- V. C. Students. Physical Growth (Folder 24.23)
- V. C. Students. Political and Social Activities, see also: V. C. Students. Social Activities (Folder 24.24a-c)
- V. C. Students. Proms (Folder 24.25)
- V. C. Students. Regional Distribution (Folder 24.26)
- V. C. Students. Registration (Folder 24.27)
- V. C. Students. Regulations, see: V. C. College Regulations, V. C. Social Regulations
- V. C. Students. Religious Affiliations, etc. (Folder 24.28)
- V. C. Students. Riding (Folder 24.29)
- V. C. Students. Self-help (Folder 24.30)
- V. C. Students. Singing (Folder 24.31)
- V. C. Students. Skiing and Skating (Folder 24.32)
- V. C. Students. Social Activities, see also: V. C. Students. Political and Social Activities (Folder 24.33)
- V. C. Students. Statistics (Folder 24.34)
- V. C. Students. Summer Activities (Folder 24.35)
- V. C. Students. Theses (Folder 24.36)
- V. C. Students. Vandalism (Folder 24.37)
- V. C. Students and Faculty, Black, see also: V. C. Students' Afro-American Society, 1897-1969 (Folder 24.38)
- V. C. Students and Faculty, Black, 1970- (Folder 24.39)
- V. C. Students, Early (Folder 24.40)
- V. C. Students, Exchange and Transfer (Folder 24.41)
- V. C. Students, Foreign (Folder 24.42-24.43)
- V. C. Students, Handicapped, see also: V. C. Handicapped Students Association (Folder 24.44)
- V. C. Students, Special (Folder 24.45)
- V. C. Students, Town see also: V. C. Alumnae Local (Folder 24.46)
- V. C. Students - Transfer, see: V. C. Students - Exchange and Transfer
- V. C. Students' Afro-American Society, see also: V. C. Students Black (Folder 24.47-24.49)
- V. C. Students' Aid Society, see: Vassar Students Aid Society
- V. C. Students' Alliance of Spanish Americans (SALSA), see also: Poder Latino (Folder 24.50)
- V. C. Students' Association (Folder 24.51-24.52)
- V. C. Students' for a Democratic Society (Folder 24.53)
- V. C. Students' Manual (Folder 24.54)
- V. C. Study Counselor (Folder 24.55)
- V. C. Summer Field Work in Archaeology, see: V. C. Archaeology, Summer Field Work in
- V. C. Summer Institute, see: V. C. Vassar Summer Institute
- V. C. Summer Institute in Chemistry, see: Summer Science Training Program in Chemistry
- V. C. Summer Programs, see also: Institute for New York State High School Teachers of English, Summer Institute in Geology, Summer Science Training Program in Chemistry (Folder 24.56)
- V. C. Summer Programs and Conferences, Office of (Folder 24.57-24.58)
- V. C. Summer School, 1982- (Folder 24.59)
- V. C. Sunset Lake, see: V. C. Lakes
- V. C. Sundial (Folder 24.60)
- V. C. Swupper Club (Swim Club) (Folder 24.61)
- V. C. Tablets, Commemorative (Folder 25.1)
- V. C. Tank (military) (Folder 25.2)
- V. C. Task Force on the Quality of Life for Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Members of the Vassar Community (Folder 25.3)
- V. C. Taxation (Folder 25.4)
- V. C. Teacher Training (Folder 25.5)
- V. C. Teaching (task force on) (Folder 25.6)
- V. C. Teaching Overseas Intern Program, see: V. C. Teacher Training
- V. C. Technology of Writing Program (Folder 25.7)
- V. C. Telephone Service (Folder 25.8)
- V. C. Telescope (Folder 25.9)
- V. C. Television Programs (Folder 25.10)
- V. C. Tennis Courts and Program (Folder 25.11)
- V. C. Tertium Quids (Folder 25.12)
- V. C. Textbooks (Folder 25.13)
- V. C. Thanksgiving (Folder 25.14)
- V. C. Thanksgiving. Dinner Menus, 1866-1896 (Folder 25.15)
- V. C. Thekla Society (Folder 25.16)
- V. C. Theses, see: V. C. Students. Theses
- V. C. Third World Festival (Folder 25.17)
- V. C. Thompson (C. Mildred) Lectures (Folder 25.18)
- V. C. Thompson Lecture (V. C. Libraries) (Folder 25.19)
- V. C. Three-year Plan, 1942/1943-1945/1946 (Folder 25.20-25.23)
- V. C. Time Survey (Folder 25.24)
- V. C. Time Survey: statistical summary of time records of Vassar College students, 1939/40, September-December 1939 (Folder 25.24a)
- V. C. Total Praise (Folder 25.24b)
- V. C. Town Hall (Folder 25.25)
- V. C. Town Students, see: V. C. Students, Town
- V. C. Traditions and Myths (Folder 25.26)
- V. C. Traffic Regulations (Folder 25.27)
- V. C. Transfer Students, see: V. C. Students, Exchange and Transfer
- V. C. Travel Bureau (Folder 25.28)
- V. C. Travel Program (Folder 25.29)
- V. C. Traveling Seminars (Folder 25.30)
- V. C. Tray Orders (Folder 25.31)
- V. C. Treasurer's Report (Folder 25.32)
- V. C. Tree Ceremonies, see also: V. C. Class Trees (Folder 25.33)
- V. C. Trees (Folder 25.34)
- V. C. Trig Ceremonies (Folder 25.35)
- V. C. Trustees (General) (Folder 25.36-25.39)
- V. C. Trustees. Circular by Order of the Trustees (378.7V I69) Index (Folder 25.40)
- V. C. Trustees. Laws and Regulations of Vassar Female College (378.7V ATp 1866) Index (Folder 25.41)
- V. C. Trustees. Committee on Endowment (Folder 25.42)
- V. C. Trustees. Committee on the Faculty and Studies. Vassar Female College: Report on Organization (378.7V BF 1863) Index (Folder 25.43)
- V. C. Trustees. Committee on Women (Folder 25.44)
- V. C. Trustees. Executive Committee (Folder 25.45)
- V. C. Trustees. Investor responsibility Committee, see also: V. C. Coalition for Social Responsibility (Folder 25.46)
- V. C. Trustees. Proceedings...Meeting(s) (Folder 25.47)
- V. C. Tuesday Club (Folder 25.48)
- V. C. Tuition (Folder 25.49)
- V. C. Undergraduate Research Summer Institute (URSI) (Folder 25.50)
- V. C. Urban Center for Black/Africana Studies (general), see: Urban Center for Black/Africana Studies
- V. C. Urban Center for Africana Studies Newsletter, see: Urban Center for Black/Africana Studies Newsletter
- V. C. Urban Studies (Folder 25.51)
- V. C. Vacations (Folder 25.52)
- V. C. Valuation (Folder 25.53)
- V. C. Vassar Bulletin, see: Vassariana in Process
- V. C. Vassar Business Association (Folder 25.54)
- V. C. Vassar Childcare Co-op (Folder 25.55)
- V. C. Vassar Civil Rights Committee (Folder 25.56)
- V. C. Vassar Close (Folder 25.57)
- V. C. Vassar College Alumni Admission Program (Folder 25.58)